emergencyemail.org 2014-12-20

# Privacy - The Emergency Email Network Homepage

Privacy Statement

* * *

This Website is owned and operated by The Emergency Email & Wireless Network an Enotem, Inc. Company We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us using our contact page by clicking here.

We’ll be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns. 

**Our Policy**  
The Emergency Email & Wireless Network uses its best efforts to respect the privacy of its online visitors. At our site, we do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not require you to register or provide information to us in order to view our web site. 

The Emergency Email & Wireless Network only gathers personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by a visitor directly or through our sponsors. For example, personally identifiable information may be collected in order to respond to a stated desire to receive information from The Emergency Email & Wireless Network. This information is used solely by The Emergency Email & Wireless Network or other entities who are involved in the operation of this site for internal purposes. We will only share personally identifiable information with third parties when the person submitting the information authorizes us to share it or we are required to by law. We may from time contact our lists to offer other services or to identify our sponsors. 

**Is Credit Card Information Secure?**  
We care about the safety and security of your transaction. We use high grade encryption and the https security protocol to communicate with your browser software. This method is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card information you send to us. 

**How Do We Use "Cookies"?**  
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected by the Emergency Email & Wireless Network’ Website through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a Website can use to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor’s ongoing access to and use of the site, and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor’s system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature. The Emergency Email & Wireless Network uses "cookie" technology only to obtain non-personal information from its online visitors in order to improve visitors’ online experience and facilitate their visit within our site. 

**Note to Parents on Our Privacy Policy**  
The Emergency Email & Wireless Network welcomes children to learn more about our organization and our programs. However, we encourage this to be done only with their parent's knowledge and supervision. For this reason, The Emergency Email & Wirless Network follows the guidelines for interactive electronic media published by the Children’s Advertising Review Unit of the Better Business Bureau. Special notices urging children to get their parent's permission before providing any personal information have been incorporated into our site. 

For information about The Emergency Email & Wireless Network and its mission, or to learn about legal or technical issues regarding the use of this site, you can contact us by clicking here.
